<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Avalon</title>
    <link>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Avalon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Avalon News for March 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/03/avalonnews/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/03/avalonnews/</guid>
      <description>Avalon Reminders  Help keep Avalon beautiful by maintaining your yard and home. Have your home power washed if there is mold on the exterior. Garbage, recycling, and yard trash should be put curbside only the night before pickup and receptacles removed by the day after pickup. Please take a bag to clean up after your dog when walking in Avalon. Lock vehicles left in the driveway and don&amp;rsquo;t leave anything valuable in sight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting Minutes for March 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/03/meetingminutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/03/meetingminutes/</guid>
      <description>Avalon HOA Board of Directors Meeting Minutes Meeting Location: 154 Sandstone Road Call to Order: 7:02 PM
Attendance  Charlie Smith, President Cindy Peterson, Vice President &amp;amp; Treasurer Debi Mabie, Secretary Doug Mader, ARB  Community Attendance  Carol Rhodes Brandi Sturdevant  General Session  The Agenda was reviewed and approved as is. The 02/11/20 meeting Minutes were reviewed and approved as is. Treasurer&amp;rsquo;s Report reviewed and approved. Ronn will get quotes from other insurance companies for Avalon Liability Insurance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting Minutes For February 2020</title>
      <link>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/02/meetingminutes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 18:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.avalonhoasc.com/posts/2020/02/meetingminutes/</guid>
      <description>Avalon HOA Board of Directors Meeting Minutes Meeting Location: 291 Sandstone Road Call to Order: 6:59 PM
Attendance  Charlie Smith, President Cindy Peterson, Vice President &amp;amp; Treasurer Debi Mabie, Secretary Domingo Perez, ARB Doug Mader, ARB  Community Attendance  Carol Rhodes  General Session  The Agenda was reviewed and approved as is. The 01/14/20 meeting minutes were reviewed and approved as is.  Neighborhood Watch  Questions were asked regarding which jurisdiction we are in, Lexington or Irmo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>